<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Memory Game Orginal</string>
    <string name="easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="versino_1_0_0">versino 1.0.0</string>
    <string name="memory_game">Memory Game</string>
    <string name="pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="memory_game_also_known_as_concentration_is_a_classic_card_game_where_players_need_to_match_pairs_of_cards_by_turning_them_face_down_the_game_is_typically_played_with_a_deck_of_cards_that_are_laid_out_in_a_grid_pattern_with_the_faces_of_the_cards_hidden_from_view_objective_the_objective_of_the_memory_game_is_to_match_all_pairs_of_cards_on_the_board_players_take_turns_flipping_over_two_cards_at_a_time_if_the_cards_match_they_remain_face_up_and_the_player_scores_a_point_if_the_cards_do_not_match_they_are_turned_face_down_again_and_the_player_s_turn_ends_the_game_continues_until_all_pairs_of_cards_have_been_matched_gameplay_start_by_shuffling_the_deck_of_cards_and_laying_them_out_in_a_grid_pattern_face_down_players_take_turns_flipping_over_two_cards_at_a_time_trying_to_find_matching_pairs_if_a_player_flips_over_two_cards_that_match_they_keep_the_cards_and_score_a_point_they_then_get_another_turn_if_the_cards_do_not_match_they_are_turned_face_down_again_and_it_becomes_the_next_player_s_turn_the_game_continues_until_all_pairs_of_cards_have_been_matched_the_player_with_the_most_matched_pairs_at_the_end_of_the_game_wins_variations_different_deck_sizes_the_grid_size_and_number_of_cards_can_vary_ranging_from_small_grids_with_a_few_pairs_of_cards_to_larger_grids_with_more_pairs_timed_gameplay_players_may_play_against_the_clock_trying_to_match_all_pairs_within_a_certain_time_limit_themed_cards_the_game_can_feature_themed_decks_such_as_animals_numbers_letters_or_images_from_popular_movies_or_tv_shows_benefits_memory_enhancement_playing_memory_games_can_improve_cognitive_functions_such_as_memory_concentration_and_attention_span_problem_solving_skills_matching_pairs_of_cards_requires_players_to_use_problem_solving_strategies_and_memory_recall_fun_and_entertainment_memory_games_are_enjoyable_for_players_of_all_ages_and_provide_a_fun_way_to_pass_the_time_while_exercising_the_brain">Memory game, also known as Concentration, is a classic card game where players need to match pairs of cards by turning them face down. The game is typically played with a deck of cards that are laid out in a grid pattern, with the faces of the cards hidden from view. Objective: The objective of the memory game is to match all pairs of cards on the board. Players take turns flipping over two cards at a time. If the cards match, they remain face up and the player scores a point. If the cards do not match, they are turned face down again, and the player\'s turn ends. The game continues until all pairs of cards have been matched. Gameplay: Start by shuffling the deck of cards and laying them out in a grid pattern, face down. Players take turns flipping over two cards at a time, trying to find matching pairs. If a player flips over two cards that match, they keep the cards and score a point. They then get another turn. If the cards do not match, they are turned face down again, and it becomes the next player\'s turn. The game continues until all pairs of cards have been matched. The player with the most matched pairs at the end of the game wins. Variations: Different Deck Sizes: The grid size and number of cards can vary, ranging from small grids with a few pairs of cards to larger grids with more pairs. Timed Gameplay: Players may play against the clock, trying to match all pairs within a certain time limit. Themed Cards: The game can feature themed decks, such as animals, numbers, letters, or images from popular movies or TV shows. Benefits: Memory Enhancement: Playing memory games can improve cognitive functions such as memory, concentration, and attention span. Problem-Solving Skills: Matching pairs of cards requires players to use problem-solving strategies and memory recall. Fun and Entertainment: Memory games are enjoyable for players of all ages and provide a fun way to pass the time while exercising the brain.</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
</resources>